Toggle navigation menu[MakeLoveNotPorn](https://makelovenotporn.tv/)

* Join The Social Sex RevolutionJoin Us
* Watch Social Sex
* Share Social Sex
* Learn More

[Sign in](https://makelovenotporn.tv/login)[Sign up

Create Account](https://makelovenotporn.tv/register)

[**Our Thankful Sale is On!**  
Sign in to get free credits through Monday.](https://makelovenotporn.tv/register)

===========================================================

Make Love Not Porn, LLC and its affiliates (“MLNP“, “we“, “our“, or “us“) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive via our Service (as defined in the [Terms of Service Agreement](https://makelovenotporn.tv/terms-of-service-agreement) available at [https://makelovenotporn.tv/terms-of-service-agreement](https://makelovenotporn.tv/terms-of-service-agreement)). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Service. Your use of the Service following any such notice will signify and constitute your assent to and acceptance of such revised Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, capitalized terms used herein have the same meanings as in our [Terms of Service](https://makelovenotporn.tv/terms-of-service-agreement).

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the products or services of our business partners or to any other third parties, even if their products or services are linked to, or embedded within, our Service. For example, payment transactions in connection with the Service are processed by third party payment service providers whose payment gateways may be embedded in the Service. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We recommend that you review the privacy statements of the payment processors and other parties with whom you interact before submitting your information.

1. A Special Note About Children
    
    Children under the age of eighteen (18) and children under the age of majority in their jurisdiction of residence are not authorized by us to access or use the Service. We do not knowingly collect information from children via our Service, and do not target our Service to children. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.
    
2. Information Collection and Use
    
    For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means information that can be used to uniquely identify you, such as your name and e-mail address.
    
    **Personal Information We Collect**
    
    When you interact with us, we may ask you to supply us with Personal Information. For example, when you create an account with us, place an order to rent Content, submit Content or payments, subscribe to newsletters or promotional materials, or otherwise use our Service, we may ask you to provide information such as your name and/or e-mail address. If you submit audiovisual Content to us, we may request additional Personal Information such as your driver’s license number and other data.
    
    This Service also includes functionality that enables users to upload or otherwise submit original videos containing explicit sexual content to us for public display and distribution on the Service. MLNP takes reasonable steps to prevent the unauthorized redistribution of videos by third parties. However, MLNP cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not obtain access to videos, or make unauthorized copies or unauthorized redistributions of videos. Therefore, the protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to the videos you submit to us. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any videos you choose to submit to us for display on the Service.
    
    We also collect Personal Information when you register to join the Service (or choose to refresh your account data) by logging into an account that you already have with a third party social networking platform (“SNP“) via our Service. For example, our Service allows you to create an account and login to the Service using your Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you create a user account by logging into an SNP via the Service, you are using the Personal Information you have already provided to the SNP (such as your “real” name, e-mail address, and other information you make available via the SNP) to create your account on our Service. Accordingly, if you use Facebook Connect to join the Service, you are allowing us to access the Personal Information in your Facebook account pursuant to Facebook’s terms and conditions governing your use of the Service via Facebook. The information we receive from an SNP may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNP, so please check the SNP’s privacy and data practices.
    
    **Our Use of Your Personal Information**
    
    We mainly use your Personal Information, either alone or in combination with other information, so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our Service and related content, products, and marketing efforts.
    
    The following are examples of a variety of ways that we may use your Personal Information. We may use your Personal Information:
    
    * to provide you with the best user experience possible;
    * to provide the products and services (e.g., rental Content) you purchase, respond to your questions, and carry out the transactions you have requested;
    * to communicate with you regarding Service updates, offers, orders, alerts, promotions, and events;
    * to help us develop, customize, deliver, support and improve our Service, products, content, and advertising;
    * to help authenticate any account you create with us;
    * to administer promotions and contests;
    * to protect the rights or property of MLNP or our users, and prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities;
    * to protect the security of our products, services, and business;
    * for our internal purposes (such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and communications); and
    * otherwise, as disclosed to you at the point of collection.
    
    If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow any unsubscribe instructions that may be provided in our communications to you, or update your user preferences by logging into your user account on the Website. Please note that we may use your Personal Information to contact you with important notifications, such as notices with respect to purchases, safety, or changes to our terms, conditions, and policies; you may not opt out of these notifications.
    
    **Social Features and Public Forums**
    
    We offer user profiles, social features and privacy settings that enable you and other users of our Service to post Content, automatically share activity information (including rental histories), or otherwise communicate on the Service in a public way. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information, or adjust your user setting to provide information, about any person in connection with your use of these features. We may use your user name and other information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum or with a social feature. Any information you share via a social feature or in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by other persons, including third parties that do not adhere to the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Service. Please pay careful attention to your account privacy settings on the Service, which will impact what information about you is visible and may give you some control over what information is shared. If your user settings indicate that your profile is “visible”, your rental activity, social sharing activity, YES-ing activity, as well as your public profile information will be accessible to other users of the Service. If you do not want information about you shared in this way, adjust your settings so that your profile is only visible to yourself (in which case your user name will still be publicly available). If you are concerned with maintaining your privacy, we suggest that you choose a user name for the Service that does not reference your real name.
    
    **Collection and Use of Non-Identifying Information**
    
    We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose information in a form that does not personally identify you (“Non-Identifying Information“) for any purpose. Non-Identifying Information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. We and/or our third party service providers obtain Non-Identifying Information about you from information that you provide us, either separately or together with your Personal Information. We and/or our third party service providers also automatically collect certain Non-Identifying Information from you when you access our Service.
    
    Certain Non-Identifying Information about you would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers in a way that enables you to be identified. However, the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other Non-Identifying information. We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other users or sources to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of our products and services, and to analyze and understand how our products and services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically.
    
    **Non-Identifying Information We Automatically Collect**
    
    When you access our Service, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies, now and hereafter devised, that automatically record certain usage information. This information may include your Internet Protocol address (and other unique identifiers for the particular device you use to access the Internet), browser type, your web or application request, your interaction with our Service, the webpage or other feature you were using before you came to our Service, pages of our Website that you visit, information you search for via our Service, access times and dates, and other similar information. We use this information for a variety of purposes, including analyzing and enhancing our products and services, and to help personalize our Service for you. We do not treat this information as Personal Information (except to the extent required by local law), although if we combine it with the Personal Information you provide, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information. We and our third-party service providers may automatically collect Non-Identifying Information using various methods, including, without limitation, cookies.
    
    A cookie is a small data file transferred to your computer when it is used to access our Service. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including to enable certain features of our Service, to better understand how you interact with our Service and to monitor aggregate usage by visitors and online traffic routing. You may be able to instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the online services you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of our online services or all functionality of our online services.
    
3. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE
    
    Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of MLNP unless we have received your consent. Non-Identifying Information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
    
    **Our Service Providers and Other Third Parties**
    
    We may engage third party companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf (e.g., without limitation, payment processing, software maintenance services, e-mail notifications, product delivery services, database management, web analytics and other services). These third parties may have access to your Personal Information. If they do, this access is provided so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are not authorized by us to otherwise use or disclose your Personal Information, except to the extent required by law.
    
    **Compliance with Laws, Legal Process and Authorities**
    
    We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of us or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable.
    
    **Data Transfer**
    
    MLNP processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. Your Personal Information may be transferred to, and used by, entities located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Such export is a requirement of providing your information to MLNP, and you hereby consent to such export in all respects.
    
    **Business Transfers**
    
    Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, we may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. It’s MLNP’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.
    
4. GENERAL
    
    **Changing or Deleting Your Information**
    
    MLNP makes good faith efforts to enable features on the Service that provide individuals with reasonable access to Personal Information that they have provided to MLNP for purposes of their user profiles and the reasonable ability to review and correct it or ask for deletion, as applicable, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. To view and change Personal Information that you have directly provided to MLNP via the Service, you can log in to your user account on the Service, or contact MLNP via e-mail to [curators@makelovenotporn.tv](mailto:curators@makelovenotporn.tv). Please note we may retain server/backup copies of all such data, and that we may decline to process change or deletion requests that we deem to be unreasonable, or require disproportionate technical effort, or jeopardize the privacy of others.
    
    **Security**
    
    We employ appropriate security measures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. These security measures include administrative, technical, and physical precautions to safeguard your Personal Information against loss, theft, and misuse. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your Personal Information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.
    
    **Third Party Products and Services**
    
    Our products and services may contain links to, or content from, third party websites and other products and services. The fact that we link to a website or display an advertisement or other third party content is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with any of those third parties, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices.
    
    We do not exercise control over third party websites, products or services. These other products and services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer or other device, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other persons and entities follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the information you submit to them or they collect from you. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.
    
    **Changes to this Privacy Policy**
    
    We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect such changes and revise the effective date included at the end of this policy.
    
    **Contacting Us**
    
    If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us via e-mail to [curators@makelovenotporn.tv](mailto:curators@makelovenotporn.tv).

Privacy Policy Effective Date: July 19, 2012

Footer
------

#### Make Love Not Porn

Pro-sex. Pro-porn. Pro-knowing the difference.

### I'm in!

### I love social sex!

### Tell me more

### The legal stuff

© 2024 MakeLoveNotPorn. All rights reserved.

Version: 8284773 - production
